[{"category":"Beginner Swift","answer":"answer1","question":"question1","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Beginner Swift","answer":"answer2","question":"question2","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Beginner Swift","answer":"answer3","question":"question3","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Beginner Swift","answer":"answer4","question":"question4","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Beginner Swift","answer":"answer5","question":"question5","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Intermediate Swift","answer":"answer6","question":"question6","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Intermediate Swift","answer":"answer7","question":"question7","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Intermediate Swift","answer":"answer8","question":"question8","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Intermediate Swift","answer":"answer9","question":"question9","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0},
 {"category":"Intermediate Swift","answer":"answer10","question":"question10","totalPoints":0,"timesSeen":0}]
